I
From the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls this is psyche awakens
You smooth mystical
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight
Tarot on deck, third eye in flight
Truths get told, egos unfold
We stir the soul with a tea surf cold
Panels be poppin', trolls be droppin'
Spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marbles fan from above
And slay the dead
It's like you're awake, hands don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
welcome everybody. Okay, I just need to address one thing real quick.
Okay, so yesterday, you know,
ghost donated again, right? Specific requests.
And I was trying to maybe fulfill those requests as best as I could while keeping the
situation fair and you know so I told them I was like okay we'll come back
it we'll come back at 10 o'clock it's gonna be like a like an hour I'll stay
up till 3 in the morning 10 to 3 if you want to right and let you kind of like
you know have fun I came back at 10 he wasn't even there and then he was at
summer so who he kicked off my show earlier I don't know everyone's pissed
I try to make everyone happy, no one's happy.
And so, what should I have done?
Like just make someone happy and like,
just make people very unhappy or just like everyone,
I try to make everyone happy.
I don't think I did anything wrong.
Well, I did come back, he wasn't there.
I was expecting him to be there.
I stayed on for like half hour waiting.
I put on SIG and on track,
well they started just rambling about some nonsense.
I didn't feel like the city like, you know
We I don't know I didn't feel like just waiting around for them to finish talking about whatever they want me whatever point they wanted to make
so
I was tired. I was a little bit tired. So sometimes I'm tired
It's not like I'm not gonna be right here the next day and help fulfill whatever request
So why did we're mad at me and be it at this morning? Oh, I don't want to do through the voice, but she's like
Everyone in her chats. Oh
Oh huge
Wait
If you want to run your show like you want to but didn't you get mad yesterday if someone told you how to run your show
And then you're like criticism for me about it
Like I don't get it anymore
member degeneration X theme song. It was like Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, like you think it's fucked, but suck it.
What upside?
What's the point of that?
We need to suck it. What's the point of saying suck it to me like the first thing?
Yeah, how you been man, I always appreciate you let me on. How you been feeling lately?
You got the glasses?
Yeah.
every time I get them you
Did you see them from a syrup? Oh, you actually bought. Oh my god. I don't steal
I'm a
Like
Give us
Because I've been hearing from a lot of people we got to pay to come up here now like we got to pay
Yeah, I actually have
I've had sponsored panels or one person has sponsored the panel for everybody and then I've given them advertising and you know
Let them animals just the closest sponsor panel
$10 for three hours
10.1. Okay, so $20 like it's six hours
Yeah, and you can you can also go in with other people and like you know say, oh
$20 right now the panel is mine for the next six hours
No, because we're telling you know the panel is sponsored and then the panel is open like ghosts for example
Was doing it in like a hundred fifty dollars and so I was to ghost I was saying okay. Well, you can
Yeah, so nobody understands exactly what happened
Know I drank a lot. I know I fucking be silly a lot
But I really am asking you questions to be serious right now if I donate $10
I sponsored the panel for three hours. Am I live to say who can come on panel or anybody can still just come on the panel
Anybody can come on. Well, I think it's my panel. It's like nobody got one. Yeah, no
Like if you pay like a hundred dollars and you said hey, like like kick this person off
I went exist first offer 24 hours, you know, it's like
All right, fair enough fair enough. I mean and it's like
I think this is actually um, this is actually capitalism. It's just I think if you're on a scammer, you're making money, man
This is rude. Whoever called you a scammer. Whoever said you're bent. Oh, it was
I mean
I like master computer
Beat has never been mean
She was this morning
I was on her show this morning Paige and Bita and
Isaiah and Jim Nick. Oh, just like you shaking your shoulders
Let me say it. Why are you like doing this? Like, oh, I was on there and it was not fuck when she's like
My ass off go ahead, buddy
Well, what about you? What were they saying? Well, I mean Jim Nick and I say they were didn't really say anything
But then beat is like oh well
You see you try to make money and then she's like it look what you're doing your bigy and she was just like here's
I see then and then just doing a cock out with allies here. Yeah, let's be the jealousy buddy
Well, let me say one thing to you that let me talk for one second, please
There's going if you're gonna do this you got to do it the right way
But if you're making money, there's going to be people that are gonna be very
Manichew because you know why they're gonna be like, oh
He found out the way to make money before I found out the way to make money
So I got to go attack him and make him stop doing that. So don't you ever stop doing it?
It was like $10 because I'm not paying your as a dollar. No, no
Today and I was also planning on doing like either like a Saturday or Sunday every week of like, you know
No free open panel like would not where I didn't do that
But I was like but I open panel sometimes for me is not very fun because it's like those love strong personalities
They all talk to each other
They all know each other and then they can go on for hours talking to each other and I think I have nothing to say in the conversations
I go back stage sometimes
Somebody in the chat made a good point. You should write these rules cuz listen
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, and then B is like, oh, B is like, well, I don't need money.
Like, well, I do, you know, it's like, I'm not, I'm not going to be your dad gives her money.
She don't need money. Your dad gives it all to her. Her Persian money or Iranian money.
Yeah, I'll burn that shit. Anybody got a match I can borrow? Thank you.
Fuck no, but she don't got it on you for that. You're making money. You're making money your own way
She lets people in her in her chat call me a scammer like I like master computer like my mortal enemy in her chat
Calling me a scammer, and she's just like ah, she really
Really? Yes. Oh my I'm just fucking around
Really that bitch
Chase me out of the room. I was like, I just left I was like because everyone's just going to gang up on me
It's not nice. I had like 20 people in the real world. Oh
No, I understand. Yeah, I'm making money on my own business. Okay. This is the job. You dumb ass Scotty
This is this fucking YouTube job. You're here. You're here being entertained
You owe him a fucking dollar Scotty for that comment that is pinned
You owe him a fucking 50 every big comment is 50 cents. If you're kind of spin yo fits like 50
Yeah, the fuckers. I'm talking to this shit
Fuck, there's nothing you'll ever know what his name was and Scott is that is that are you Americans?
You know, it's not very polite to ask somebody how much money they're making
I'll tell you I'm making money and I'm making money more than 99% people making money on YouTube. Okay, 99% of money
I'm in the top 1% of people on YouTube making money. Okay, and that's not like
A lot most people on YouTube don't make much money most people don't there's people making years
I mean, yeah, it's gonna be jealousy. You're gonna
It's gonna be a lot of jealousy when you start making money off YouTube with all the other like Sam
Man, no offense to Sam, but he's gay Sam Ampita
They're all gonna be like holy shit
Psych actually found a way to make money off of these panels and we weren't smart enough to do it first
So we got to attack him and make him feel really bad about it
And I don't stop doing it and then we'll do it and then we'll say like thanks like for me the innovator
Even though we bullied you. I mean they sit
They they mean they would get monetized for the fact that they'd like the n-word so much, you know, I don't like it
So I don't really say it every five words every five words
No, no, no, no, not you do it, please so anyway
Hey, I'm British. How are you I'm brisk? Good to see you. Thank you for being here. Yeah, I don't know
It's just a little controversy though. I know I got some very nice donations. I tried to
Keep everyone happy.
Don't move to Maine Night and drink it.
You get out of Maine Night as this caretaker,
yet he forgot it's not a Southern state.
I have no idea what that means.
I know who Maine Night is, but I have no idea
why Maine Night would be my caretaker.
I don't need care, not yet.
Give me 20 more years of beer drinking.
Then I'll need somebody to wipe my ass.
Sorry. Yeah, I just want to know like, you know, like, so like last night it goes, you know, he kicked off summer and then he said, okay,
Well, there's anyone to kick off for steam for see that just donated to kick off somebody and so she just donated
Sure, but he was he said all he wanted was summer and then he's like he said he saved the rest for later
As for Christine, I said, since Christine just donated,
I'm going to have a rule.
If someone donates that day, then they can't be kicked out.
Like immunity, immunity, immunity, immunity, immunity.
Yeah, so he was, so hey, Alex, how are you?
So yeah, so anyway, so.
But then Christine's not happy summer wasn't happy ghost wasn't happy and then everywhere else is like oh look everyone's upset
It's like it. Let's all right
Listen to me psych. I'm only playing along with your things cuz I'm like buzzing
I don't care what you do with your money
But you're not ever gonna if you think you're gonna make everybody happy
It's never gonna happen. So don't try to make every single person happy some you can't please some people you can't make happy
So tell them to go fuck
but they want to come here, come here, but you ain't going to be happy about it.
Yeah, and I know it's like a mix of my fucking pitchers falling apart.
Yeah.
But yeah, and so it's like and I wasn't just gonna like let goes like be like think like okay
Even if someone donated like a million dollars if like I can't have somebody coming on and like porn bombing
You know like I can't have
Or even even for $200 or saying oh well, it's like why should just I should have the control control because I don't
Yes, you don't know a lot, but I still have to worry about TOS. I still have to worry about
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I think it's if I just I have to stream every day you're saying though. I can be the show just alone just talking alone
Not Sam and because he's gay. No, okay. Yeah, I mean it would be like that basically
Be like just like, you know show at the end of the show
I mean it was just probably I just like it probably ended and the show would just keep the million dollars and move to an island
the
it was a reference from the big Lebowski, I don't know if you've ever seen that man
it's like, oh, I'm on the Rubik's Cube, yeah, the more you try it, the harder I get
no, it's the Rubik's Cube, because he's working
nope, big Lebowski's family invented the Rubik's Cube, that's how he had money
that's why he was like
Yeah, Bonnie, it's not a fun year. You didn't see the big Lebowski though. Okay, never mind
Yeah, I have John Goodman's in it. Remember what he fucking took his handgun and was like you want to fucking pull them off fucking lanes
Yeah, remember when John Goodman had a heart attack in Roseanne. I remember crying as a little kid
the
Fisher beat her up and Dan just gets his coat and walks out of the house and you know damn well
Dan's gonna go over there and that cops after the next scene the cops were at Dan's house like you fucking beat up
Fisher you gave him two black eyes Dan and Scott
I know I know okay, so guys got
So Scott's is why I get so so Scott doesn't work Scott gets retirement
He says don't knows don't pay for SSI retirement. Well, I don't get SSI retirement my friend
I don't I but I do pay taxes that probably do go to your stupid SSI and retirement then so, you know, just leave me alone
We're paying for you
Anyway, and it's under your business
What is it anybody business what anybody makes so why is it only but if I'm making money, then it's a big deal
If anybody else is making money. Oh good for the if I do people are getting up in arms
And I'm so much like and I'll tell you one thing please real quick. I know I'm talking about the one thing
The other day, Sam-Man, I like Sam-Man, I know I keep talking about him, but I do like you, Sam-Man, if you're watching.
But he maybe so aggravated the other day, it was like two weeks ago, because I had to go to work on a Friday.
It was like, I woke up at like seven in the morning, and he was on a live.
And he like, I could hear him open his fridge right, and he's like,
I'm gonna get my little drank-drank on a Friday, and I'm thinking like,
I gotta go to work and sweat all day, and you gonna get your little drank-drank?
Like, if I got your little drank, drank, say, man, I'll fucking take that bottle and snap it over your fucking head.
Sorry.
Yeah, I'm just saying this meal.
Do I get up when you're 65 it depends on what you do the previous 65 years?
Okay, Scott
Beer or drink drink and if I ever do he's not gonna be my friend anymore like don't you fucking call beer a drink drank fucking
Joe Joe Joe, did you see the copper wire from everybody in America? Did you were you the one that?
Why do you think I'm drinking fancy beers? Why do you think I'm not drinking natural lights? I got the fancy beer today boys
Thank you. Thank you guys. I know I got people to get it. It's just like
Especially people that are my friends. I think you know my friend might say hey in private, you know, it's like hey
Well, it's like you know, I'm sure
No, I've buttoned buttoning it but people
Okay, I'm okay. Let me take a piss. Okay, but people were like ganging up on me and then like, you know
Then someone named not nags was in like her chat say, oh, well, you know
It's the same bad things and I was like, I was like, you know mind your own business nags or whatever
And then you're like, why are you yelling at nags? And I was like, well look what they just said like that's not nags
That's not nags. What's the same thing to me? I don't know who the different do nags and not nags
I mean it says not nags. I thought it could be sarcastic. I mean
Yeah, but anyway, okay, so people are mad. Okay, but you know what? I tried my best to make everyone happy
I think if you see my behavior, I try and it's like just because I was you know
I was on for I'm one 25% of my day yesterday six out six and a half hours or seven hours
I was on live. Okay, and so
That's like a long time, you know, it's like, so I couldn't wait, you know
I told him to meet me at 10 o'clock in the room
He decided to go hang out with summer who he had just kicked out of my room
So so I waited for him for half hour. He didn't show up and I was like, okay
Well, we'll do it later
But I didn't have time just to wait around the man. It's like
Okay, so protect yourself that's
Now say one thing to you soggy
People see your happiness. They see how happy you are streaming right now. And you know what they're doing in their heads
They're thinking what the fuck's he so happy for let's get let's get his ass. That's porn bombing. Let's
They just they're jealous of you man. Like I've never seen somebody wear a tablecloth before but you're wearing a shirt
Even though it's not a shirt. It's a tablecloth. It's still cool. It's still pretty cool, man
Yeah jealous of you man. You've been doing your thing
I mean, I'm trying. I mean, it's like and I
Summer I'm having fun, but it gets like words like people like always think it's like oh the always people like pick on me
Oh, oh, oh, thank you my gosh. Thank you so much for the cash up. Thank you so much
I don't know
You all see it because I don't know if you want to be anonymous. I don't know what to be anonymous
If they don't want to be anonymous or they want me but I want to thank you for the cast. Thank you so much. It was very sweet
I want you to know my brother
451 at six o'clock in one hour from now at six o'clock. I've been planning this out
I'm watching every Hulk Hogan match. I ever loved at six o'clock till the day I died just tonight. What up J1?
What up big dog?
Yeah
Quick question
I know my Yankees suck, but I was thinking you take the Oreo should clean house like fire everyone
They should give her the general manager
Well, they're going to get rid of the coach right now is the interim coach. They already fired our coach
The interim coach are gonna give it up. I don't want to talk about baseball much, but you know 100% they should you know
Here's what I would do listen to me J1
Adley Rochman has two years left on his contract.
I would trade Adjie Bushman right now
and get what I can get for him.
Because we got a catcher in the minor leagues
that can come up and replace him.
Do you understand what I'm saying, dude?
I could run this fucking team better than him.
I'm sorry, Psych.
He asked me a question.
I love my sports.
Yeah, sorry, but I love my bones.
Okay, that's what it's called. It's sports balls. This is an open panel for everybody today
Like every note no exceptions. Okay, so no exceptions
What the hell is that sexy piece? Oh
God damn you look it's fucking sexy as hell summer. God. I need the fucking term
There's not next
Jamie Jamie Cowboys need to lead not next from the the chat, please just hide them please because they've they've been talking shit
Be is this morning and now it down my chest, so so so please
Not next not it's an it's not it's not next. I so it's not that actual next. It's just the
Personator, but um if you could take them off Jamie. I appreciate that
Okay, don't say the next word, please. It's Saturday. I'll take a ball and get with psyche
Yeah
Bitch last time I seen this summer. I'm sorry about this
It's okay, baby. Oh, no, I
Met the Jay one that's what I was told to Jay one the whole time
No, I knew it. I knew it. I knew it wasn't me
the
Yeah, I mean, I'll let everybody today today. Let's have a let's have everybody on let's say get up
I want everybody to be happy today. Let's let's have everyone happy today. Let's like
Let's do them a great day guys. It was a little bit like summer last night. I told goes I told ghost last night
I was like ghosts. That's like, okay. Well, let me just take an hour break
I'll be off from ten o'clock till two or three in the morning if you want
$350 and then you came over and hung out in my shit and then he gave me he gave me 30 bucks
last night because I thought I was kind of fucking with them but I was like oh no you did all this
to take my voice away for two days you got to pay 50 bucks to come up on my panel he got to 30
but I thought if he could come up but he was just hanging out in the chat uh yeah
See or it looks like that on it looks like venom and her matches or tattoos. That's what I liked about it
But so much sites like oh, yeah, I'm sweetheart. Love it
Second fucking something's happening here
But yeah, and then so anyway, it was just like I was just you know
I was fine and then I was like, okay
I'll take everything tomorrow, you know
And then I was to beat us and then everyone was just like they're already they're already talking about me when I got there
And then then I was like they're watching for a few minutes and I started typing in the chat and then they kind of just like
Jumped on top of me like oh like and I just left but I didn't I don't feel like I did anything wrong
Clean of YouTube, so don't you dare talk about Michael? I'm not talking badly better
I'm saying she was saying things about me
I was like I didn't say one thing about her ever like I did not care how she if she won't know if she wants to charge
Or not charge or you want to
I think she's just trying to figure out how if she's gonna do it how to do it that you know what I mean
Summer no offense BG in the chat said if he stood on two phone books and was just always you could he kiss you on the lips
That's what he's asking like if he's
I'm only five foot tall, so I don't know how many
I'm only five feet tall, so I don't know how many phone books you stand it on I'm little
Time I see him he's getting trapped into a fucking little
What it's be baby be da
Okay, she's famous. We just famous now. I'm being serious. She's fucking famous. Go ahead. It could be a trick though
It could be a porn bomb. It could be it. No, it's not it's not it's not a word yet. She hasn't said a word
Hi
You're saying you're being really sarcastic about like you're like, oh, well, you know, I'm gonna charge like a dollar a minute
Like I mean, and then you're like
I was talking about one person was Alex and one TV was trying to join my fucking panel the whole time
No, you guys were doing that
Oh, yeah, what about you? Yeah, listen, listen, listen to me right now, okay?
I get a lot of people that come over there really upset
really upset about what happened every freaking time you take a donation and you end your live or
somebody gets clogged or like somebody else so i it's not the first time okay so i always tell
them i don't know what's going on i don't know what the deal is okay no i'm not telling you
They're not telling you the truth, which is like I did I told them I come back at 10 o'clock at night
And I'll be on here for like five hours and then I came back at 10 waiting for like
The truth is like certain people that come out of there would like a bad taste in their mouth because they did pay a lot of money
And then there's other people that I'm not going to name them. They can defend themselves, but listen um
I don't know why it's so upsetting for you to have honesty like right in your face. It's like
That you didn't know what happened you didn't know that I told
I told
Ghost to come back at 10 o'clock. I'd be there from 10 to two and
Talking shit about you like why is psyche making money? Why is he doing that? I was like literally saying
I don't know what's going on the rules change all the time. It should be pretty basic and I know there's like
Um, a couple of people that I care about females that have to pay a lot of money to have some assholes to abuse them. I don't have to deal with that. I just like
I
Okay, so in the case
Queen it was my issue. It was like the only person that I said has to pay to get on my panel last night
Okay, so maybe a fucking whore. Well, I thought you would be I thought I thought you I thought you were being sarcastic about like
Oh, well, you're John's heard. So it's like, you know, I'll start Alex
Before like, um, you know, I went live
You know on backstage that you know if alex is here i won't be here and i said he doesn't even need to be here
I don't give a fuck it's easy peasy for me
He's not that fucking real and i stuck to it and i even said if you give that money
It's gonna go back towards somebody else that you fucking you know
Yeah, i'm not gonna
But I bet I didn't but every fucking chance I get you're like bringing up my name way. I don't know but be that be that it's like
Because because the last thing I remember is I went to your chat this morning and then it's like and then
Watch little sections and watch like like, you know not have selectable. What you hear you're like
I watch I watch for an hour before I said anything in the chat. I was I said they're watching
What was I saying about you? Go ahead? You're kind of you're kind of you're gonna say you're saying oh, yeah
Well, you want to make money you see it. You see like now you have all these problems and there's
like right you said that and then more money you make the more problems yeah but I'll tell you
like the thing was he wanted to kick out pristine pristine had just donated so I said
If you donate that day, then I'll give you immunity that day and I didn't feel like kicking Christine off and stuff
Everyone happy
And then you got an allied master computer calling me a scammer your chat. You don't even address it
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. So you're now people cannot have their own opinions in my chat either. I say calling me a scammer
Call me
All kinds of fucking
Alexander gets on every single time and you just ignore it you leave your panel and you just let them rant on and on and on a lot
Well, I was in like I was in trouble right now
You just got the service attack
Smoke your weed psyche. Don't listen to her
Okay, so I gotta like delete every comment of everybody's opinion. I don't give
A lot of shit about me too
Like if you know you don't have you let people call me a scammer be you called me a scammer and you said oh
I'm not good at tarot. It's like oh, oh, you're gonna see paid paid is great as hair, but you know
To the need cards paid to the need cards, you know
Oh you scamming I never said go to fucking psyche or this person
I said they have their different ways of doing psyche greetings. You're this quick
She does like more in depth and that's it the fuck
See now you're on the show
I'm gonna show you guys because you are constantly saying, you know, you're like, oh
True bank Bonnie the jealousy is gonna start they're all gonna come up attacking you and look what's happening
I called this, you know, I should be a terror car reader cuz I know the future baby
Well
Me the only way they'll get clops is with money, you know, I just leave I just go get the money here
You told me several times like people have gone too far like Arthur that time I kicked off Arthur
I think I have a lot of people that you've asked me to and then it's like and then let's say weren't really doing anything
Then I didn't what do you think you kicked off arsara?
I can't afford because you're like it was he said the uncle thing and then it's like
A lot of people for you before beta
There was no monetary system that you were playing second of all it should be the principal anybody
That's calling somebody or and talking about someone's family is automatically hate like take a break and you know
You're diverting from like your problems and my problems you're bringing other people's name into it that person said
Why are you attacking Saki? He's not even doing anything.
You're saying he's breaking Nate.
All right, I'll be quiet. Let me stop.
Let him fight.
Yeah, because anywhere all everybody was talking shit about
and beat us, beat us, beat us.
Well, you know, the fuck?
They were. They were.
After I go there and people,
and everyone in chat is talking shit about me.
It's like, you know, so,
it's like, it's not a very friendly chat for me anymore.
And it's like, and then when you do it,
that really hurts my feelings.
Bikie when you take a bit, you know when you take a donation like that you've got to respect the money and stay live
So people are gonna get mad and come in there. They were having you or else to go. So they come over there
Lift your panel like with a better taste in their mouth. Okay
The way you did it fuck me to the donator was happy with the what you cut it off then be the conchisher
It's the porters big supporters up
No, it goes would have been back at 10 o'clock
I would have stayed there until two or three in the morning with him
That was supposed to be his night since like the side, you know to like we're kind of run the panel
That was like I named the whole thing after him. I was there on time, you know, and I was there
Okay, but it's like your opinions you is very harsh and it's like
You know you I always say I always say I always will come you there all this fucking shit
But I'm gonna be real with you. Yeah, I am gonna be a real deal. I have been with
Really taking all of you you're fucking bullshit, and you're putting it out on me. So other people
Not everybody has a chat with 100 people in it, okay, so you have a chat with 100 people you have responsibility to at least know the story like
not to allow certain people saying shit that are disgusting I don't I don't
get off that open it's definitely that to me I mean it's like I kick people off
the panel all the time for that okay it's like it maybe all the time let's
say how many people Alexander McQueen fucking attack
page, summer, Kristine, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander, Alexander,
Okay, but you've had a lot after you've told him to meet a band him like and then you were you've had on after that
And so it's like you know downhill you got paid you got paid
But you agreed with him being banned for permanently and like and you were upset that you got brought back, right?
You're upset that I'd like to refund to Tracy that time like because I
made a fair
Fuck that you need to do I'm just telling you like, you know
If I see somebody comes over there and they're actually hurt and they need to that they're gonna talk
So who is her?
You know, like the panel don't come to it. What are these guys trying to beat up for?
No, no, these guys are trying to you about me. Why are they crying to you about me?
It's very confusing like when it comes like to the monetary system it confuses them because it's like
You just like we're annoyed one day by like somebody's like smile or something like that, you know, yeah
Yeah, so let's say you have 25 even rule and so I have a rule of 25 dollars pick someone up like uh, or 10 dollars
People get upset and come to invent a nice parking chat. No, but you're not
You're not telling, you're not repeating the story right, like if you don't know the rules, you can look in the description of the channel, there's like two lines, they're basically one line of piece to how simple the rules are, okay, but then sometimes because he donated so much, okay, well that's, what do we do now?
Do I just like, you know, I can't like, refund the super chat, so I'm gonna be like, okay, I'll work with you, but within the TOS rules, within their show rules.
I mean, sorry
Sike him on his channel in a fucking way you once you come up here and cry about it, but it's still like channel baby guy. Oh
Yes
You're not allowed on the panel because you need to pay up and then you have a place that you want to go to and then you come
To mine. We'll talk about that later. Okay. All right. Bye now. All right
Okay, I don't know
Whatever the fuck you want. I don't really give a shit. I still like like view. I respect you
But I'm sorry if people get upset and they come to me. We are gonna discuss what I'm like always like what happened now
You hear the part of the story where I
Not always being talked about there's a lot going on in my life. Okay, I know but I know when I know I know when I am
I know what I know there is I know there is but at that time I was and I was just like a coincidence
But it's okay. You you promote me. I promote page Tom
the same thing. So don't bring a page who's better or this or that. Now it's like,
I'm not bringing it to bed. If you know, you brought that up. You brought that up.
You said that. Yes, you have. Yes, you have. And you said,
also your ex boyfriend was better at me than reading, right? It's like, and so it's like,
you are insulting my, my perspective.
What's that guy Carl came up here and was like
No, no cuz he was on your show talking shit, and I was there that day and I heard you
I said I said ex-boyfriend beat I said ex-boyfriend. Yes, and I guess you were there you're kissing us, but you're like, oh
Well, it's like you you're you he has to read cards. You don't need cards. It's like, okay. Well, whatever
It's like I don't need cards either, but it's like why are you?
do i do i talk about you you're thinking way too much about this fucking bullshit people talk about me all the fucking time people are gonna have their opinions you know i mean yeah but it's not like it's not like
this is a point it's like words like
slander of my business and it's like of my like I've always been honest
I gotta protect my chat and say nobody says that because it slanders his business but now when I'm on your panel
I gotta be called or fucking this
It's you slattering and not
He's always where's that fucking witch? Where's that fucking beta? Where's that? Oh, I fucking decide. Hey, I can't stand or god
I mean you fucking say nothing nothing
Everybody's here's called you a bitch or a witch or they called you a whore, but you're a witch. Hello anybody there
Anyway, okay. Well, we can come down. It's like, you know, it's like, yeah, we okay. Well, we got it out
But the beta it's like you didn't understand. I
Leave the panel and like oh that would sound bad. I'm like, oh I took no I took money and then I left the panel
No, I didn't I like I ended the show and then I started I said I'd come back at 10 o'clock and he decided to go
That's what people told me happened. Okay. Okay. I know but how about your my side of the story?
It's like and then I didn't even like talk last night and then I was like well nex is like in the chat saying
horrible things to not and you're like, well, that's not
Link yesterday. You can take the link anytime you want. Just come up here and say whatever, you know
Yeah, well, I would I would have it. It was not it was not friendly
I like said this this is the presence of that like what the fuck yes
All right, my moral and my moral enemies right now have a channel taking down
Always did a scammer you don't want you'll address it. You don't say well. He's not a scammer. You don't say oh
He's you know, you know, he'll work it out. You're like you're just saying they're agreeing but that everybody is so it's like
It was another friendly
Know what happened with necks? I have no idea what the fuck you're talking about. You're bringing up somebody's name right here
It was not next in the chat and I was talking to them in your chat like telling them to like leave me alone
It's a fake nags. They're in the chat today and they are gonna kick out of the chat. They're in here right here like um
They're like see so on
It's indirect. Yeah. Oh, there's okay
This is a real neg and then there's a but it's a person that says not nags the fake nags and that's who I was I didn't know the difference
But uh, yeah, so I apologize if I got I got not nags and nags confused that they have nags in the name
So it's confusing. Okay, so anyway, anyway, hi
Who's the other nags? Okay, I'm sorry
I'll try to find it.
Oh, here it is, not nicks.
Right here, that's a not nicks.
This guy says, not nicks.
Anyone else who's doing this, it's
like he's going to dox them and their family.
You will feel the pain.
Wow, wow, but that's really nice.
That's really nice to say.
I
Like doesn't come really from my channel. They're not one of my mods. They're saying it in your chapter
I'm responsible where people are saying it was last night in your town
It was in your chef this morning this morning when I came to your
It moves really fast. I know I know I know that's what I was saying. I was saying
You can talk shit about me as long as you don't talk about people's family no doxing none of that fucking shit
So people's opinion people call me they say I'm a fucking I you know
I do this this and that but it's like if you think that you're not you don't have to be so upset about it
You know, okay, well, we are well
Okay, yeah, well, I mean of course I get upset when I like, you know, and I feel like
Like no one has my back like absolutely no one did, you know, it's like and so
No, no one knows this story
A lot of people don't have my back a lot of people have my back
I don't fucking know but every time somebody gets like
Talk shit about me every fucking time you like especially specifically people like Alexander mayors. You don't give a fuck
Alexander McQueen you don't give a fuck you just you just let them say
You know how he's even gone about like uncle shit
Yeah, he's he's insulted me
countless times
Personality, you know, he was like telling me it's like what you got a nose job you little spoiled, you know brad like, you know
So that's his personality, but it's okay like you're okay with him because he's you know
One of your donators and like one of the people that you know, but he hasn't donated in a long long time
You know, it's like so it's not like oh, well, I'm so worried it's like I
I'll make it you know, I'll make donators mad sometimes, you know, I can't like make everyone happy
I'm trying to keep everyone happy, but it's like you can't like so I made nobody happy it turns out
But I tried to make everyone happy because my intention was good. It wasn't like I wasn't like sitting there
They're trying to milk somebody or anything like that
I mean, it was just it was a price to me that I was getting the donations and I'm thankful for them
And I'm grateful for ghosts and I'll be able to do some really cool something really cool
I'll be able to probably get a computer now that I've been like
have been able to get for like five years, you know, and so I'll be able to, like, upgrade the show and
spice it
Go ahead, Bita. What about that?
I'm gonna attack him for that and get a new computer now for the donations
I don't give a shit what I don't give a shit what psyche does with the donation
I will be get all the fucking money, but don't fucking blame me for what's going on
Like when it gets messy over here and people come over there. Don't blame me. I can't just be like hey get out of here
Who was mad though last night who was mad like was Christine mad because Christine I didn't kick off the show
I didn't like I told you know
Uh, she'll ghost, you know, Christine just donated. I'm not going to kick her off today. And so I had her back and I would have been back that night, but he was gone. And so, I mean, I would have stayed the whole night.
It's been over and over and over again. It's not just like it's always, it's like your rules changed, okay?
Because rules sometimes have to change, you know, the laws change, you know, because it's called progress
It's called like, you know, oh, we have to tweak something because this is a work. This is a work
You have to give me a chance to like, you know, I had the basic
This happens a lot. So people come over there and they're like, I'm upset. I got kicked. I didn't even say anything
I paid somebody paid and then that does that's enough
Yeah, they're not telling you if they annoyed me, you know, even if
People but other people don't perceive it as like being it. They were like, you know annoying me or something like that
They were annoying me so I can kick them up. You
If people want to go really far and they're like, oh, let me look make fun of them
Let's show like a video or just I'm like, I'm not doing that fucking shit, you know
Canada I did show the video didn't you show the video on your show? I mean, okay. No, he didn't I wouldn't let him
Well, it's been it's been seen though, but so he's sort of somewhere, but I you know
I think summer might have been there I was like he keeps saying oh, I'm gonna share I was like
No, I don't want to see it
I don't want to fucking see it and then you keep
Like he needs to keep the pores away the what the poor me the poor, okay?
How about by Down syndrome?
Avatar
So that's why you're in the back now, bitch
That's why yeah, and I just banned them because it's like I was not only was an offensive photo. That was just an offensive
Stupid thing to say too. So whores. What does that mean? I mean is to see you're being really dumb and so I don't know
Poof jeez. I mean Casey like and see that it's people like in the case he probably is one of those people that went over two years
And he went to Emma's and stuff like that complaining. Oh, he's letting me out not for some reason
How about just like he's a boring guest and he does his microphones bad and
Annoying and he's not even Casey hasn't even been on my panel. I know I'm gonna say on my panel. I'm saying I'm saying, you know
Like so it's like
No, I can it is just you're already admitting that there's a bunch of issues with different people that you know
You have issues with and they like not I'm not saying you know
It comes back as part of the streaming is part of making money like you can't blame everybody else for having their opinions or
Sure, but you're like, oh, people come over to my chat so upset about like how you
Okay, fine there. They're they're always happy. They're like, yeah, okay, that's fine
People people like kz who like kick off for good reasons and it's like and then it's like
KC hasn't been on my panel. He might have been in the chat, but I don't fucking know. I have no idea
He wasn't on my panel at like
It was a couple weeks ago, maybe, or a week ago, and I'd not let him on the panel, and
then someone said, oh, he's at fetus right now.
I'm trashing you.
And then they're like, oh, well, now he's at Anna's and her Discord talking about you.
So whatever.
It's like, go ahead and...
whatever you want to Emma or whatever, I do not talk to her, I do not have any.
Okay, so anyway, I'll calm down. I'm calm down.
And Bida, I'm sorry if I was wrong or jumped to conclusion or something or wrong, but it's like,
I would like to at least like...
It would have been nice to hear some like stuff like one like positive thing about me
But it's like it just seems like a lot of negative every time I go to
Hear what you want to hear. That's negative. There's a lot of positive things about here. I want to hear the truth
I want to hear the yes. I don't know yesterday when I went on with
Yesterday we were you were on the panel and I guess I don't know I said let's say Keith
I just said that I just said that I said yesterday it was awesome yesterday when Alexander was on it was like that was like
That was like one of the best like appearances
Later on and I just don't even know what's going on
Your title is not about you people come over there and they're upset and I'm like, okay
What's going on now and then it was talked about maybe a little bit
It wasn't all night and people in the chat like I don't fucking know they say a lot of random shit
Okay, oh, I'm over I'm over it. I'm over it. I just wanted to I know I got I got out my emotion about it
I'm not emotional about it anymore. I'm I apologize and you know and so I'm apologize if anyone's unhappy
I I will be here to like work everything out and it's like
I'm sorry that you felt like you know, I was attacking you personally
I just you know, I'm gonna be honest with you and that's it and um, I don't know what's going on
But I would say if you are you know, make your rules like very very clear very clear, you know
Yes, and guys, I do have the rules in my description and sometimes there are unprecedented things
Like but I haven't dealt with and I have to deal with them on the spot
And I'll try to do my best to be fair and you know equity equanimous
But some maybe somebody's not gonna be happy, you know, and so I do apologize, but I'm trying my best
I'm trying my very best and it's uh, you know, that's all I can do. So that's it
Okay, I'm sorry. Okay, I'm sorry if I apologize to me. I didn't like you don't have to apologize to me
I just don't want to be blamed like you're like beta. Pita didn't do this beat on beat us beat us beat
It's like I heard my name. I'm like, what the fuck like I just come up here and defend myself. Yeah, because I
Have that moment you're in the chat and you're like listen that come up here and be like hey
This is what happened, but you're sitting here and you're like I
Would have been I would have been with an unfriendly it seemed like an unfriendly
Well, I wouldn't be able to like, you know, it's like everyone had their opinion about it
And that's like a lot of people against me and it's not comfortable to like have to like
Really not comfortable I always let you up there
But it's really not also comfortable up here trying to talk when Alex is yelling over you like calling you fucking war
And this person should be this and beaten and this and this and that I know it's really really uncomfortable
But you know you just kind of go with it, you know
Well, but I really thought like Samantha would just give me the stream
You're like some random stream and I was just gonna click it and then like being some guys random stream
Thank you, Samantha. I'm sorry. I called you a horror earlier. Sorry about that, sweetheart
Go ahead beat a tax psyche for making money. Hello
God yeah, all right. Thank you attack Joe for fucking like putting this shit on me. Do you see it?
They're not joking. They're not joking about me. They're not joking. They're not trying to joke about me. They're they're they're saying like horrible things. Okay, so they're not
I told like
People that come up and are jealous and be a man of you and then be the joint in his man and jealous
Right. I should be a tarot card reader because I had dug. I mean I said it would happen. What the
Okay, we have a new guest, we have a new guest.
Let's welcome our guest.
Let's see, we have Tita Arano and Solo.
Hello guys, what's up?
I don't know, I thought it was Montrose, dad.
Oh, what's up?
Hi, hey, what's up?
Have you been here before?
I don't recognize you.
No bro, JP told me to fucking come visit, so I'm here.
Okay, J.P. Okay. Well, y'all at us. I mean, they're gonna yell at us man. I said, I said J.T. J.T.
I love you. I love you. I'm sorry. Okay.
Hey, yeah, good. I always love baby beta
Most people know me, uh, most people know me by uh fire fires one fire fire. You can call me auto though
You know, it looks like a barber doesn't know you though like this your barber know you because if that's a hair cut
He gave you that motherfucker should die
I
First of all, I want to know who the summer girl is well. Hey, she's sexy mama
Actually now I like it now I'd like this
His hair cut looks really
Bro, I call it like I see it bro. And when I saw that, I when I saw that woman right there
I got something you can see right now. Hold on. I got something
Hey Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, hold on, Joe, hold on
I got it
Let me talk, let me talk to you guys
Okay
I like this guy so autos, so um, so where are you from?
Burbank, I don't know give you exactly, but you know, East Coast, West Coast, or I'm an LA personally
But you don't think
Okay, cool. Yeah, we've got a lot of Canadian viewers here. Awesome. And so high solo
How'd you are you friends with auto?
No, I was wondering if they had a Jalisco restaurant in Canada
Okay, let's go ahead and ask them that Jalisco restaurant in Canada. Do you guys went out the dinner before that's kind of
Yes, I think yes. I think yes. I mean, it's it's gay, but it's cool
No, oh, yeah, it's happy. It's happy happiness joyfulness. Yes, Simone Wayne
Yes, okay, it's happy
Upon a point you I want to take her out the dinner because I know she
Joe Joe Joe go in the chat for Joe go in the chat for a few minutes that I want to have a nice
Pleasant conversation go talk to Ivana in the chat. Okay. Okay, so, you know, I like to I like to talk to the new guests
Okay, so so JT or JT told you about this show. Okay. Awesome
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Okay, well are you interested in like, you know, I do tarot or
You know different things like that what it what brought you here like what exactly like now
I've been doing tarot for a long time. Oh, you have you ever?
Have notebooks full of it. Uh-huh. And also I have animal messages cards. It's my favorite
But I've had real life experiences with animals
that, you know, certain experiences are messages, you know what I'm saying they're profound like you can see an animal
It doesn't necessarily mean it's a message, right? But sometimes
It's extraordinary and you recognize that you know, it's an animal so-called animal message
Yeah, an animal like an omen or like a yeah some kind of it will animals all of animals have a very
Like most of them have a talent or most of them have a specialty or something like that
It's something that maybe a gift that maybe humans don't have and so
You know they said when they handed all the gifts to
All the gifts to the world they give them all the animals first and then they didn't have anything left over for for man
So they made a woman, but um, yeah, so that's in the Greek mythology the story of Pandora if you're interested, but um,
Yeah, so
Yeah
But yeah, I would say animal omens are very like you find out the symbolism of if you see an extraordinary or out of place
Maybe animal even if you see something on TV sometimes it can have a message for you
If you know, you'll have a kind of a feeling about it, but look at the animal means
I've never had it on TV, but I've had numerous real-life experience with animals that were
Extremely significant in my life
Okay, can you tell us some of the some of the animals that you've come across again in
World owls my mind. I have owl medicine. So I've seen owls warned me and
You know the first time I happened I was unaware entirely unaware. I didn't know right
Yeah, I was of course are like they're nocturnal. They like they sit and they basically watch they have their eyes wide open
They their head turns around 180 degrees and so they can see a full like full
Radius around them and there's very there's very specific actions and activities if you witness it and experience first hand you'll know
the
well one of them is the death of a loved one
that's one of the primary ones
death of a loved one okay
I haven't really heard that before but okay so that's interesting
so maybe foreboding yeah some animals like you know there's the banshee that forebows death and there's certain
well I'll play this the set the Native Americans say our first nations
saying is if the owl flies over someone dies
Okay, so it's a bad omen. It would be considered an inauspicious omen to see
Lucky or unlucky for you
What do you consider it you consider you and my experience it was a painful
Okay, but it doesn't
But sometimes motherfuckers sometimes people need to die, you know
Well, everyone will die of course, but I mean so I'm just saying we did somebody die after did you have the you have some kind of
experience where you know a close one died or was it
numerous times
Okay
One time the I've been flew over my head twice like in like less than a half a second
So let me see I'm gonna look up the Indian symbolism for an owl and see
What I see awesome blue thumb
Yeah, because that is very interesting. I mean, I basically heard like you know, I would think you know if I was to hear an ally go
Who who you like, you know who it's a WHO or like, you know or something about watching and something like that
I was out medicine
made of American
Okay. I mean, they are also in India. They may have different meanings.
It says in many Native American traditions, the owl holds powerful and complex symbolism,
often associated with wisdom and foreboding. They are seen as messengers capable of seeing
beyond the veil of the physical world and possessing the ability to traverse between
the realms of living and the death. However, some tribes associate with owls with death,
bad luck, or even witchcraft, particularly when owls are seen or heard at night.
Okay, we all know about Jareth so sometimes we leave a certain medicine men are witches could shape shift into owls to perform harmful magic or spy on others
The perception of owls as connected to dark magic contributes to their negative symbolism in some communities
Okay, so yeah, it seems like you're you're right. They're messengers and sometimes they bring messages of death and foreboding
And it's like some native people are fearful of the owl and call it feathers deceiver feathers
Sometimes the medicine of sorcerers and wishes it says under al medicine bear blend calm. It's a it's like a good website
Let me check out for well this mythology what you read. Listen. What you read doesn't make me right
What makes me right is the fact that I have a
In-depth experience on what I'm speaking on
Right like you were at some shit you read some shit off the internet dude like I have a self-experience dude with this shit
Right, but that's your own. That's your own experience my friend
And so if I mean if I had my own experience I could relate that to you
But I'm trying to like tell you well here's traditionally what the owl said to me and I
Verified it before you actually it was like where you said was no verify verifies the wrong word doing like
Well, if it was like if it was like if the mythology about the owl was all positive and nothing about death
And then you had said that I was saying well, maybe that was specific to you or something like that
But you're saying well, it has to mean this and because it happened to you
Because you see an owl and then someone dies that does not it's not a causation
Seeing the owl did not cause them to die right and so it's like there's not is there a really relation there
but maybe
It has to do with your what exactly what happens. It's a very interpersonal has to do with the exact interpersonal
Relationship and experience do it's more complicated. That's what I tried to preface what I was saying
With it doesn't mean because you see it now doesn't mean anything, you know, I tried to preface it preface it with that
But you do but you are saying does mean something because you're saying I had a meaning to you and I meant a specific thing about death of
Sort of people and so I was trying to get I'm trying to figure out like exactly
What think what had what you know what the causation was like or it was in an omen was that kind of thing
But it's just because you know
of all of those people will see it as a lot of people will see an owl that will all those people have something that dies, you know, it's like so
no, no, no, absolutely not, yeah, because, yeah, I've seen tons of owls and nothing happened, dude, like
mm-hmm, mm-hmm, definitely not, yeah
well, what was special about the one, that, that particular one that was, that stuck out
well, okay, I will repeat the saying, this saying that I'm saying goes deep into history
this is this, this is the saying from the native First Nations people
when the owl flies over someone died
Okay
Yeah, and then you said but then you said the thing interesting you said well
He's some people deserve to die and like or something like that. So can you explain that part of it? Oh?
Well, that's more personal
like
Like I think that's my opinion that people deserve to die, right?
Well people I mean people will die everybody will everybody I mean so everybody will die right and that's not a question
It's just matters when not the answer is when not if if right so everyone will die
So I'm some of these things that people does that deserve to die early or something
I'm kind of like what's the point the whole point of the story. I want to hear the point
The message the message you're trying to convey. That's what I'm not I don't have a message. I'm just trying to my brother
I'm just trying to hang out dude. I don't have a message
Okay, I'm not asking in like a mean way. I'm just asking that one understands what where you're coming from. Yeah
I'm sorry. Yeah, I don't have a point. I don't have a point dude. Like I'm drinking some my point is I'm drinking some beer
I'm about to roll a joint
Okay, and and I'm just chilling, you know saying and like well, I forget I I forget y'all said something that
Peaked my interest so I decided hop on the panel and I forgot what that was to be honest
Um, well, we had beta on right before we were talking about I kind of forgot. I'm sorry
We got we go to kind of a different lot of different topics, but uh, I don't know
We were talking about you know reading
Cars, no, no, you said about terracotta. I do terracotta. I've been doing terracotta ever
I have notebooks full of fucking terracotta reading dude. Mm-hmm
Good, I'm a dude. I love terror cars, dude
I think this is I think this is for real dude because I've done so many terror card readings and they become it proved
It was accurate with the crazy part is
Is when I try to use the terror cards for a sports speculation and gambling it doesn't fucking work
But when I do it for like hardcore shit, it does work
Right, because the spirit world is not very interested in humans making money gambling or finding treasure
But that's kind of what a lot of humans have just been interested in when they when a petition this the spirit world sometimes
And so if you especially if you ask something that's not selfish or something like you know out of like that
Actually like maybe help people or something like that
I think spirit is more apt to get involved and so it's all about you know
That's why I've been asked if I can predict sports betting and all kinds of things
by tarot cards and I'm like, no, I'll just guess for bedding and stuff like that. It's a misuse of the
I think it maybe have to do with the interpretation if you're a skilled interpreter
because the thing is I've contacted Spirit World and they've told me exactly what was going to happen
in a two-year period of time, but I think that has to do with the certain spiritual aspects and like
really not shit
It's not it's not looking for money. It's like it's like it's like I'm saying it's like, you know
There's there's people that just use in the occult and things like that to find very sure and we are hidden things like it's like
Yeah
Spears I think you're in the treasure. I think I do with purity. I think I was with purity like a
there's certain of
Out of I'll put like that a purity like through a channel purity you could communicate
and find out the future and it's that's what I just said is in the fucking movies and shit, dude, like
Right. Well, we have to be careful with movies too because they like to present an image of magic that is not necessarily
What I'm talking about all personal experience my brother
Okay, yeah, I understand and I'm not discounting your experience. It's interesting
I just want to make sure you I just wouldn't be sure I understood where you're coming from
Yeah, I was I was I was throwing I was throwing it in as an additional fucking cookie
You know that you want to talk to cookie like a chocolate cover or go as well on top. Okay?
For you man, low cookie low extra cookie man. Okay. Well, I mean it's like
Yeah, so this was that really okay. Let's let's take on the topic, please. Okay, well
Whits what I'm God he is God
cheese
So would you consider yourself really in touch with your
What's up, Shirley? I would actually consider myself retarded. I'm
Bro, some seeds to school. That's what I'll say about that. Okay
Summer do what do you think? Oh, do I sound good right now? What's up?
Ask me I'm the host, okay
You hear me yeah, okay, he's got you better know
Everybody sounds good on the panel. Oh, there's three sexy ladies. Who the hell are they supposed to be keep the screen up?
Okay
Like any of those ladies, but I'm just saying never seen anything close to them
It's page on the right beat it in the middle and then it's a DG Electro on the left
No, I could say cage, but that's beat it in the middle get that shit off that screen
Get it off my screen. Okay. Hold on. No, I can't
I'll go like this. That does
Who's that cartoon Johnny Depp? Is that supposed to be you psyche? Yeah, I don't think so buddy
Where which cartoon Johnny's terrible? That's one right?
I would hear like a cartoon Harry man. You put you showed that
Looks just like yeah, I'm looking at his coffee. Oh my store bugs. Yeah, I know you put that star bucks
I have some other other stuff. I've been making these new cars. Let me see
Yes, I'm not a couple cars to read for you
Shut the fuck up Joe. Hey, so like why you letting yourself admitted in cell on the panel
The guy hasn't had been late for like a three years and he has a terrible fucking voice
I don't judge anyone there
Who cares who cares who has sex or not you know
Well you should
We're human beings
Who cares if we ain't had sex in ten years
I don't bother
There we fucking go
Does it matter Joe? Who have you had sex within ten years like a goat?
Nobody else besides your fucking mommy
Joey doesn't have to talk about people's families in that way and it's also you we don't know
We don't know who's we don't know who's lost. We don't know who's lost their mother. We don't know
We don't know what if we did have sex with a guy's mom. You don't know
No, you can't ban up for that dude like what if he's what if he's fucking the shit out of it right now?
I think you know what? I think this is my show I can do what I want. I can do what I want on my show, you know
You don't tell me what I can do it off
No, it's not it's going up. Hey, the spiritual realm doesn't want that fucking Joe guy here. Okay
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, I mean, I put up with him as long as possible
But I mean, it's nothing to do with you know
People's mom so I wanted to ask you about your stream title
You said free open panel like like you have some sort of show that you're you're like you're good on your own
And you don't need any guests like your guess don't make your show
I don't I don't I am that interesting. Okay. I don't need all I need is a summer myself to talk
I don't need I don't need any other any dumb guys, you know telling me they're repeating this stuff
Are you there summer?
I think I might have. Oh, hey summer. How are you? Yeah, I don't gosh that they didn't they really don't like people get a word
We're an edgewise do they?
I'm sorry that you were
They all had their something to say they had they all had some points to make I just don't know exactly what the point was but I
Just got that icky feeling so
Probably the one big voice sounds familiar, but I just don't know where I've heard his voice at before
With the the the auto guy not not sure
I think it's the first time he's been on the show. Uh-huh. Oh, okay
Oh shoot. I don't know. No, but dude they were saying he was three tarot cards. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, I think his name is Otto
And he said JT sent him over here. No, there was the other guy. Oh solo solo the guy's solo
Oh, I thought it was okay
Yeah, well, I've been warned. He's a poor bomber. Joe is like back
I roasted them back here remember
Okay
Joe just sit back there for a minute. Well, how about I wouldn't ask you
Well, I kick God he off because God
Left the backstage he left the backstage, but you know, it's like people tell me
They I don't know if I have a feeling to kick somebody off. I'm just gonna go with that feeling because I I have
Intuition about things or I have like, you know, I just get a feeling
I know you haven't I know I know you have but I was saying don't talk about
Yeah, you know
You know, it is the worst thing I think first of all mothers should be respected. Okay, first of all
I don't like to yell mama jokes or any on anybody's
Yeah, but there's a cheapest kind of joke
Where it's like, you know, it's like
Little kids go yo mama yo mama this yo mama that that's a maturity level that we're dealing with when people are like
Your mom now you're saying it now. You're saying it now. There's an example. I
paraphrase
Example but yes, yes, there's an example guys. I
Wouldn't a fucking example
Anyway, I say anyway, I'm not gonna have people disrespect me on my panel even if it is open panel
As far as as far as I leave the door open and it's like I'm not gonna be disrespected on my shelf
That's part of the reason that I started the sponsoring the open panels because people were just being very disrespectful
And like I basically didn't matter if I was here or not. They just wanted the platform
And so I just want to
Make sure that I'm involved in the show as much as I should be and I say one thing, please
Can I say one thing please summer a better an hour ago when psyche went live?
I told him you're making money. You're doing your thing
There's going to be people that hate you and are jealous of you 20 minutes later
Vita comes up cussing him out saying he's doing the wrong thing. I'm telling you psyche
Okay
Yeah, she's entitled to her opinion and she
Here though stop pushing your fucking ear
My ear, okay, but we're like 30 seconds. Give me good. Go ahead. Okay. You would know a good show
But slap you in the face like the last black cock
Oh, who was he talking about who did he it's talking about you Joe. Okay. Anyway, okay
Well, that was that was that was worth bringing somebody back up
But you see guys, you know once bitten twice shy anyway
Yeah, it's like I don't feel like dealing with a bunch of nonsense
It is my show and it's like if I lose my entire audience I can build another audience, you know
I'm not concerned physically about that. I would I would like to you know
I do have so many great people here that, you know, I would hate to stop doing the open
panels altogether, which was what I was going to do, basically, because they are very time
consuming.
They're very energy-strapping.
And then if it's, like, just to be disrespectful and a bunch of cases slander me right in my
face, I'm not going to put up with it.
And so, or if I do, then I'm going to have it monetized.
What's the word like you know like some chump or something like that?
So anyway, I'll run the show like I want to run the show you like it you can you don't like it
Don't let the door hit you on the way out. You know, it's like guys. I'm concerned about
The audience that does care not a bunch of people that are gonna be impossible to please and it will be impossible
There's nothing I can do right in some of these people's eyes
And so why put any effort or energy into that I'm just gonna put energy into having the best show I can and
You don't like it
That's your problem
Yep, so that's not so good so
But what is it Saturday? It's a nice the beautiful day Los Angeles a little bit overcast. Oh, yeah
It's sitting here cuddling with the cat. I
Have a really cool book summer. I want to say this book. I got summer. It's really cool. It's called
This is called this book will change your life
I got this this is on Amazon and you can see it's just like really it I'm probably gonna
pause sleep just so you know oh it's exciting but look at me look how exciting it is it's
guys just like full of pictures and it's like basically you do it you do an activity a day
and it's like something that you probably wouldn't do I'll just read like one little page let me see
this is a very short read I'm not telling you not to read I'm I'm tired I've already done
Day two says today the love of your life is a today gaze at everyone wondering whether they might be the one true love of your life
The one destined for you and you alone and whether you might be passing them by forever act in consequence
Then it says notes. So that's just no just like an example of all this stuff like little short
Things like one page a day you can go through a page a day and it looks pretty interesting
Like this one, for example, it's a day 253.
This is Aunt Roberta's, this is Aunt Roberta.
This is the strongest cocktail in the world, okay?
Aunt Roberta, the strongest cocktail in the world.
Invite a friend over today and sample it.
It says, two shots of absinthe,
that'll be hard to find, it's illegal in the United States.
One shot of brandy, three shots of vodka,
one and a half shots of gin, and one shot of creme de mure.
Shake well and strain into a martini glass.
Now I wanna try that.
So and invite a friend. That's the strongest cocktail. Yep, and Joe just loves that word cock
Okay, anyway, Crystal should be a little about Crystal is welcome up
Everybody's pretty much welcome up and I'll give him a chance like you know case he had brought up even though I'd
Pretty much his band and then he disappointed me again. And so and then
Occasionally that will happen but anyway
But I do hope
Okay summer, okay. Well, thank you for being I thank you for coming and I love you summer and
I'll be here
Okay
Okay, I don't think I will shout out random guy. Thank you very much for this donation and thank you for this donation and
Thank you very much. I appreciate you. You're a superstar even though you
Came on assaulting me and stuff, you know
That makes it a little bit easier to take
Anyway, okay now well now we have a brave array of joy and sunshine coming to visit us
So
Well, there it is. Oh, yeah, there it is
Oh, are you doing?
I'm just fabulous. How are you doing?
Don't all right. Oh look your buddy's here. Oh
Hello
What's up? What's up? How are you? I was on your stream last night and they kicked me out. I didn't know you didn't kick you up. Your camera died and then you disappeared. But I swear, we did not kick you out. I would not. You're so cute. Why would I kick you out?
You see, this is what happened last night.
to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to be allowed to
OK, OK, now it's 100 no fests.
You look like a fucking Harry Turtle in a way.
What's up, Joe?
That's my boy.
Hey, I told you I'm a Harry Turtle, man.
Ain't talking to me, boy.
I ain't talking to you.
I don't know you.
Hey, Joe.
Hey, Joe, why are we banned from L.D. Stream?
Why are we banned from L.D. Stream?
I'm not banned from L.D. Stream.
I respect the L.D.
You're the one that cries the L.D.
Why do my ex-wife leave me?
They probably left you
because you're wearing a wig on your head.
You're wearing a Bruce Lee wig.
That's probably why your ex-wife left you,
motherfucker.
He's calling.
It's not a wig.
Sorry to psych you.
Oh, that's your actual hair that's even like fucking I thought it was a wig you actually grew that out
I'm sorry, man. Who am I talking about? Look at this. Who the fuck am I talking about people's hair?
Talking about this guy's hair, okay, bring back
I didn't kick him up he left on his own
When you cut your head to psyche, at least psyche,
that's what you want your hair to look like, like psychies.
That's what a man would like to look like,
got a nice grown hair, nice beard to compliment it,
and a 10-inch cock to light it all off.
You don't understand that?
Suck your shit out.
Again, little baby bitch.
I wish I had it.
Can I turn my camera off?
Sorry, because I'm about to show my fucking weakness.
Hi, guys.
Okay, so yeah guys mods. Can you like keep an eye on chat a little bit and people like, you know, the same things like
Okay, okay, okay. Okay. We'll see you. Hey, Joe. Do you want to see something cool Joe?
Yes, what is it your asshole
No, let me see. I'm fucking me. Just like you. Let me see it. Are you there? You're frozen
Ooh, what is that?
It's like the bowels of hell.
It's like the guy sitting on the throne of hell
with two like little slaves, like a woman and a man.
And the man is so short, it looks like J-Dog.
That man is like the height of J-Dog.
I'm glad you showed that to me.
It's like, thank you actually for that.
It makes me laugh.
Like, hey, J-Dog, were you here?
That's you, nigga.
I made your lamp at least, go on, you didn't make me laugh, you made me shout out, hey, don't say that, okay, so
Let me let me pull my shirt off so you don't have to see my second chant. Thank you. Okay
I'm doing some
Person yeah, whoever that I don't know. No, that was not me J dog
There's the pool
I got another one big
I would I guess I'm actually making out a man plus
Man that looks like same man when he's homeless like walking to his homeless camp
Look at my little fucking
When you have a fucking stick with a bag on it like a fucking bomb thing
But you know, there's my there's my professional professional
That is not you that is not you psyche. Come on. Yes
Brother
Let me see him over time please because you had a cat on your shoulder. Let me get a good look at it, please
It looks like you're cat though. I gave it
It does it does
You look better than that pictures like you you look better than that man. I know
Okay, I like better than that
Face that guy has like a fat. I need to get a piece back now. Look at the fat. Hold on. No
Here it's like good times. Maybe it was like that. Oh, don't even say that don't say that they're page. Look at this page
I like you don't age like page. Okay. Oh
That's a little like be baby beat. I love beta. I love the fuck with her, but I really do like like beta
I'm not gonna say I love her. I don't even fucking know her, but I like her a lot. You know her
When you're really man, it's like we all get drunk and sometimes I get too drunk
If we all get drunk at the same time, it will be a perfect scream and it happens every once in a while
the
My my original goal before white two-pot went live was to watch get drunk and watch every Hulk Hogan match in the history of Hulk Hogan
WrestleMania 3, WrestleMania 5, WrestleMania 6, WrestleMania 7, WrestleMania 8
The creation of the NWO
I'm a Hulk Hogan fan. I was born in 1984 and I'm telling you right now
80s kids are hurting when Ozzy Osbourne passes away and then Hulk Hogan passed away two days later
Any 90s kids out there? I feel for you, man. I'm one of them and I know
Hulk Hogan more like an 80s star like I mean he seems like a very
Times is live. I see it, but I'm not gonna leave right away. I'm gonna give him a little fucking second to wait
Suggie, I mean this from the bottom of my heart.
I remember one time when I was a little kid,
me and my brother wanted to get the Royal Rumble in 1991.
And my dad was like, we were bowling.
And my dad was like, if you bowl a mark, so not a strike, it could be a spare.
I swear to God, my first ball went into the gutter, I did not get any down.
He probably would have ordered it for us.
But the next ball I rolled knocked down all the pins.
So it wasn't a strike, it was a spare.
But I remember my brother jumping into my arms like, yes, he's going to get it!
And I held him up and the whole balling out was like what the hell's going on over there
And I was like it's love is going on you pieces of shit
Get your eyes off us and as I held my brother up and he was like ho again ho again
ho again
And I'll admit I cried the other day when I see my childhood hero Hogan passed away. I shat my fucking tears motherfucker
Yeah, but you you're in a lab at that psyche
I've laughing at spunky a spunky
The problem was I was trying to make it look like you guys and I was like that I would every time I type
I like to pull my head between her tits and her just take her tits and bash my brains out
thank you Spooky
Spooky, I tried to do it like when I ever asked specifically draw the devil car with like I said a blonde
Busamy woman and a like a man that looked like Mr. Clean
And it kept saying, oh, that's a obscene.
And so I had to like ask him a thousand times.
And finally, it made me think what it made you.
I want to go to good times, but I want you to know I don't take
doing your panels for granted.
I will donate to you.
I know you think I'm a piece of shit that only joins your panels
when I'm drunk.
Don't donate you any money.
I know.
And that's not wrong to think.
But I will light you up soon. Okay, big dog. You're a friend to me
So it's not all about money for me. It's about you know, call me a friend right now
You're right. You're right. You're my friend. You're my friend Joe. Thank you for being my
I'm gonna go late on my brother good times. All right. See I'm gonna guess he mowed the grass again. All right. I'll be back
Yeah, see you buddy
And guys if the people that I have done cards for I really would like I need to start collecting if you could like
But somehow when you're backstage like just remind me and I'll give you my email address
I need like if I can have like a headshot like a photo just so I can make the face look like you're
Exactly like you or like it's more similar to you if you want me to do that. If not, then I'll just have like the
Inspired inspired by you know, but if you'd like to have like, you know be actually be more prominent then
Yeah, so I am building a website right now. I've already created my
Banner for it. Let me see if they can have a look at it. Hold on a second. Okay, there's Jesus
Well, I see exactly what you're doing. So you let up these these on these straight fucking in cells
Because you know you want to tackle a straight man like that's what the gay guys want to do, huh?
And you feel that being that he doesn't have pussy and so long he might convert I see what you're doing. You're smart, dude
I got you
Do your thing boy
You figured it out. You figured it out. You figured it out. I did. That's why you have Joe up so much
You think he's gonna cross over, huh?
Yeah, I just like I have this thing about street guys. I guess it can't get enough of them
Keep chipping out of my thinking my work. I will we have what we have made out before you've seen the video, right? So yeah
Yeah
You'll get there
That's my banner so far. I don't know. I mean, I might redo it, but you know, that's working on it. Okay
I'm building a website. So that's what I got so far.
No, it's not AI. It's the banner I made on Canva.
But I mean, I did get the picture of me as AI.
Um, yeah, but I made that for come on. I was like, who made that for you?
I did. I did. I made that.
Hey, let me see it again.
Yes, I did.
Hold on.
Okay.
I just use two of my logos that I have and then I put a ticket like I got like three different logos for your brand
Which one do you want what you can't all three of them? No, no, but they're gonna be mine
It might be that's the top banner, but it might be but maybe I'll make you smaller something like that
I mean, it's like you gotta make up your mind and pick one. You can't have all three. It's like why I want to get
It's like a hold on like a Nike symbol than an Adidas symbol then a fucking Puma symbol unless all the same thing calling it your brand
There's gonna be different like umbrellas that I do to take talk for instance and so I can have a link to the take talk
I can have a link to the YouTube on one of them. I mean, I'll put down you don't find that confusing like a brand is like to
Identify who you are. You won't have three different brands. Well, yeah, there's a lot of
Manager here dude. I'm my own man. I'm my manager. I'm my producer director
I'm my fucking I'm everything. I'm the director of the fucking next is either the animals the animal trainer the guest booker
I actually know a gay. I know a gay animal trainer on these you to on these YouTube streets. Yeah
Stick freedom away. Oh, Roy. There you go. He's a dog trainer though. He doesn't do cats
Okay, well cats are hard to train, but they can be trained though. There's actually rushes. You don't hear much about training cats, do you?
Well on America's Got Talent there was that these Russian ladies that were able to like their cats would like kind of jump through like hula hoops
And like walk across like little like um tight tight rope kind of things, but that's all they would do
I mean, it's like basically
Can already do that is cute. They're truly dependent man. They don't they don't want to be trained
Yeah, but they but they can a little bit like you can you can kind of train them a little bit like you know
But it's get to do a very very very slowly very very patiently and it's let the cat do what they want to do
But this day they do like to occasionally
Like you know you can make you can like train them with food and stuff treats and motivation and stuff a little bit
But yeah, they're hard to train
They're very independent. You just want to be rubbed. You're gonna be rubbed and you're gonna be back in your shit
My girlfriend's cat. She actually fetches the cat actually fetches like she'll throw the little ball with a bell inside of it
And the cat will run down the stairs and grab the ball and bring it back up the stair
I've never seen that but the fucking cat does pretty cool. Yeah, it's cool. It's different pretty rare
Yeah, well my cats will sometimes like I'll throw I'll throw some stuff sometimes and sometimes they'll go run and get it and then
Occasionally, they've kind of brought it back near me, but not like a dog does. You know, it's like very
They don't really
Want to please as much as the dogs do them
Thank you. Oh, I can't I love sleeping with this guy. He's a little cuddle bugs
He goes under the covers and you sleep with me all night and then you lick my nose to wake me up in the morning or the afternoon
I feed you
Good boy
See what kind of what kind of cat is your girlfriend? How I
Don't know is there a different
It was free so I doubt that it was like a pure-blood cat
Mm-hmm. Well, sometimes you can tell if they're science. I am either like I have a cat that kind of was like a main
Coon a little bit and different depends on
With the dad and the mom are but yeah, they have some
Because my my last cat had two tuxedo cats and they had tricks and then I had one that looks like my other
Oh, that's what it is a tuxedo cat. Yeah, it's a tuxedo cat. Okay
black and white
No, those are very sweet cats and black cats, too
Like I've never
Mike my black cat is pretty much one of the sweetest cats I've never even know cats could be the sweetest
She is she likes a kiss. She likes to
You know cuddle and
And these are the cuddlers here that pretty much are in the house like tricks Lenore and Lola and
I haven't seen marbles in a little bit. I think marbles is out wandering
Oh, I think he comes back every couple months. Maybe
Well, you have a cat that goes away for a month. Yeah
He's a boy and so male cats tend to wander and so he's more of like a he's a little bit
Wild at this point because he's been he's gone a lot of the time just out out
You know going through the neighborhood
Male cats tend to look for a female and we'll go walk them for miles trying to find the female meowing so oh here's ghosts
Hey, good
You're see you're what's up ghosts? Yeah, how you doing, bro? Okay? How are you today good?
Good good good good. Oh, I miss you last night. Oh, I'll uh, well, I'll be I'll be always scheduled for you
But I you know, I said ten o'clock last night. I can't I came back and you were at summer
So I waved around a little bit. Hey, dude. Yeah, I don't
Okay, well, we'll do it. We will do it, you know, I do OU and I really do want to thank you so much for the donations and things like that
I'm gonna probably be able to get a computer now. It'll really improve the show
I'll be able to do a lot of cool things like share more videos and stuff and
What are you using?
I'm just using an iPad and my my phone and I have a spare tablet too
It's just a cheap Amazon one that I can't even mod off of
There's also on team. There's some really good deals on like use laptops for like there. There's like Apple
Apple yeah, but don't you have to be careful? I don't know. I've never bought anything off team up
Don't you have to be careful buying stuff off of that? Yeah
Yeah, and especially because they are they do seem like they're it says conditions some of them are good very good
Some are good and some of them are like a little bit like one of the windows has windows 11
Is the windows 11 the current one or is there a new windows? I'm not sure but it might be an older windows
I don't
Haven't had one forever. Also, I haven't been able to play video games forever
I have over a thousand of steam games like games on steam, you know
I just haven't been able to play any video games or anything, but um, I
Have VR. I have a VR headset that I can't use right now
And so maybe I really want to be able to do beat the VR stuff
So I'll see all the computers now are like these little mini there's a little tiny like little computers and they're getting really cheap, so
Smaller and they're getting more powerful. Yeah
Even like and the TV sets to like they're I saw like this Amazon 32 inch TV on Amazon for 60 bucks
That's how much for flats, you know flat screens. So TVs are getting really reasonable too. It seems like
You know, so that'll be pretty cool. Maybe I can get another another monitor or something and show some stuff off that and
I don't know, I think it will be, I think it will be good.
So, oh yeah, Leisure to Larry, yes, I played Leisure to Larry, I played all the, Ilya,
I played that when I was a little kid, my brother was in college, came back from college,
he had a computer, this is like in the 80s, late 80s probably, and he had a computer and
he was like, he's like, look, and he's like.
Pull up they had like these programs with like nudity like a playboy like thing
But it's like it would take like five minutes, and we're just slowly like it was just like slowly like
Five minutes, and then it was slowly like open the picture. It'd be like a naked picture
And but uh, yeah, you you play Larry. Yeah, it was all pixelated. I'll buzz you
It's like whoa that was like I was like the porn back then and then I'm at leisure Larry is a really fun game
It is a pretty pornographic game, too. It's all about this kind of loser guy
and he goes trying to find his like a girlfriend and he keeps me beautiful women but
and weird stuff keeps happening. Did you watch the movie uh what is it called Pixels? It has Adam Sandler in it.
Adam Sandler, what um has Pixels? Yeah it was weird like they uh Pac-Man and all that it was it was a funny movie.
I don't know I've I've been seeing Adam Sandler moving for a long time but
yeah he's just. Did you kick that old boy and he leaves?
Now he left he left I can't get you but I don't know if you I did kick a few people today because
You know, I thought that they were being kind of rude, but
Yeah, you're always cool
Respectful were there?
Yeah, I mean, it was like, you know, it's usual, but it's like I just want to I want to keep it
I want to keep it friendly here. You know, I want to keep it. I want to keep it good. I don't like the
negative I mean if you if they were
Don't want to be rude, but if I when I say smart enough
I don't actually mean it
But if they were if they would do it the right way there is a way guys
You could if you really want to argue you can do it in a friendly way, believe it or not
It's like don't even call it debating but you can do it in a smart way
We can get your point across and not be rude
right now if your arguments like right the same the wrong way
Yeah, that could be an argument
But you know you have to have evidence of that but what I'm saying is you can actually argue. I I'm actually I actually
Don't do it most of the time because you know, I do like sometimes I like to get into the debates
but yeah
Well, yeah, I
Try to let everyone speak though me. I'm like that I literally pay for people to speak well once they take it too far
That's like you just
Some people can't help themselves with one inch up. Here's a ray. Okay, hold on random guy. Yeah
Don't know what's up. Yeah, I put him back